{
    "subject": "resource/Get_Carter",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of Get Carter is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9416177272796631,
            "question": "Is English the primary language used in Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8419127464294434,
            "question": "Is there any other language besides English used in Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7934465408325195,
            "question": "What is the connection between the film Get Carter and the English language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7899109721183777,
            "question": "Why might the filmmakers have chosen English as the language for Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6961992383003235,
            "question": "What language is the film Get Carter spoken in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6248010396957397,
            "question": "If someone doesn't speak English, would they be able to understand Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.603719174861908,
            "question": "What language would a viewer need to understand to watch Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.592127799987793,
            "question": "In what language was the dialogue for Get Carter recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5348491668701172,
            "question": "What is the main linguistic element of the film Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49155083298683167,
            "question": "How does the use of English contribute to Get Carter's overall impact?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Get Carter is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7254_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main linguistic element of the film Get Carter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7254_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what language was the dialogue for Get Carter recorded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7254_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language would a viewer need to understand to watch Get Carter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7254_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7254_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple \"The language of Get Carter is English\". This is explicitly stated in the first document, where it says \"Language: English\" under the movie details section."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"Country: UK\" and \"Language: English\", which supports the triple that the language of Get Carter is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}